Beatrice Murphy Campbell
DC Public Library Special Collections
Beatrice Murphy Campbell Collection
1979-1989
DC Public Library, Special Collections
0.25 linear feet; 1 box
123
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Series 1
  - Biographical, 1978-1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Incoming Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1978-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - District of Columbia Commission on Aging, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - District of Columbia Statewide Health Coordinating Council (SHCC), 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Beatrice M. Murphy Foundation, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Retired Senior Volunteer Program (RSVP), undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Speeches and Testimony, 1979-1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Speeches and Testimony, 1979-1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Clippings and Newsletter, 1955-1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Awards - Handicapped Person of the Year, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Awards - Handicapped Person of the Year, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Awards - Women’s Hall of Fame, D.C. Commission for Women, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)